Elihu Vedder
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1804-1951, Series 2:; (Boxes 2-5; 3.6 linear feet)
  Kingston, William Beatty: 1883-1885, 1888 (see also Reel 2323)
  Kinnicutt, Lincoln N.: 1897 (see Reel 2323)
  Klapp, Laura E.: 1898, undated
  Knowlton, D. R.: 1874, 1876
  Koehler, S. R.: 1880, 1886
  Kollops (?), T. E.: 1884
  L
  L. Prang and Co.: 1881
  LaFarge, John: 1884, 1894, undated (see Reel 2323)
  Lagata, Emma: undated
  Laffan, William: 1884, 1885, 1891
  Langley, S. P.: 1894 (see Reel 2323)
  Lasell, Mary K.: undated
  Lathrop, Kate S.: 1898 (see Reel 2323)
  Lathrop, S. P.: 1883
  Lay, Oliver J.: 1866
  Lewis, Ethel Black: 1913
  Library of Congress: 1915
  Lieber, Henrietta: 1893
  Linton, W. J.: 1880, 1884, 1887
  Lloyd, David D.: 1885
  Lloyd, H. D.: 1887, undated
  Lloyd, Jessie B.: 1885-1887, 1889, 1890, 1893, undated
  Loder, John: 1884
  Long, G. W.: 1866
  Long, George A.: 1892, 1894
  Long, Mary E.: 1867, undated
  Lord, Austin W.: 1896, 1898
  Low, John J.: 1885
  Lowell, Georgina: 1869
  Lowell, J. R.: 1875 (see Reel 2323)
  Lubin, David: 1908
  Ludlow, Anna D.: 1894 (see Reel 2323)
  M
  Macantrey, C.H.H.: undated
  Macbeth, Wiliam: 1910
  MacMillan, Amy B.: 1896
  MacMillan, George C.: 1894
  MacNeil, H. A.: 1900
  Madonough, A. R.: undated
  Malloy, Edward C.: 1951
  Matterson, T. H.: 1879, 1880
  Matthew, Frank: 1897 (see Reel 2323)
  Matthew, Leah: 1897 (see Reel 2323)
  Matthews, Brandon: 1904 (see Reel 2323)
  Marburg, Theodore: 1877
  Marks, H. Stacy: 1876
  Marrs, Kingsmill: undated
  Marshal, J. B.: 1863
  Mauley, F.: undated
  Maynard, George W.: 1910
  McClurg, Mary Virginia: 1889, undated
  McGraw, Jennie: undated
  McKim, Charles F.: 1894, 1895, undated (see Reel 2323)
  McLeish, Fannie: 1872
  Mead, Olga: 1893
  Melville, E. S. (Mrs. Herman Melville): 1896 (see Reel 2323)
  Merriman, Daniel: 1892
  Merriman, Helen B.: 1892, 1893, undated
  Metropolitan Museum of Art: 1883, 1912, 1938
  Meyer, Rose: 1890 (see also Reel 2323), 1891, undated
  Miller, (Hepburn), Edith: 1891, undated
  Millet, Emily: undated
  Millet, Francis D.: 1878, 1891, 1894, 1896, 1897, 1899, 1907, 1910, undated (see also Reel 2323)
  Millet, Geraldine: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Millet, J. B. (Houghton Mifflin and Co.): 1882, 1888, 1889, 1891, 1895
  Millet, Lily M.: undated
  Moen, H.A.R.: 1880, 1881
  Morgan, George O.: 1901
  Morgan, Harriet M.: undated
  Monks, George H.: 1887
  Moore, Mr.: 1881
  Morgan, E. D.: 1874
  Morgan, J. Pierpont: 1875-1877
  Moulton, Louise Chandler: undated (see also Reel 2323)
  Munroe (?), John: 1878
  Mural Painters Society: 1895
  Murrar, W.H.H.: 1889
  Musgrave, George: undated
  N
  Nardi, Gunhild: 1947
  Nevin (?), B. J.: 1882
  New England Magazine: 1895
  New York Times: 1900
  Noyes, Emily M.: 1886-1891, undated
  Noyes, Walter B.: 1884
  O
  Osgood, J. R.: 1865, 1883
  Otis, F. N.: 1875
  P
  Paige, J. W.: 1876-1878, undated
  Parkesmith, Mina: 1890 (see Reel 2323)
  Parsons, Alfred: 1889, undated (see Reel 2323)
  Parsons, Anna: undated
  Partridge, Augusta: 1889
  Partridge, William Ordway: undated
  Patterson, Emily: 1892 (see Reel 2323)
  Paul, Daniel: 1880
  Peard, F. M.: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Pearson, John C.: 1911
  Peck, Tracy: 1915
  Penfield, Mr.: 1896
  Pennington (?), Harper: 1911 (see Reel 2323)
  Perkins, Clara Crawford: 1895 (see Reel 2323)
  Phillips, C. H.: 1891
  Pittsburgh Dispatch: 1894
  Powers, Mrs: 1910
  Putnam, Elizabeth Munroe: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Q
  Quaritch, Bernard: 1886, 1907
  Quartley, Arthur: 1882
  R
  Reinhardt (?), Charles S.: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Rhead, Louis: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Richmond, Clara: 1880, 1881, 1894, undated
  Richmond, N. B.: 1897, undated
  Rinehart, William H.: undated
  Rives, G. L. (The Century Club): 1892, 1893
  Robinson, Frank J.: 1883, 1884, 1888
  Rodin, A.: 1909 (see Reel 2323)
  Rogers, Elizabeth B.: 1877-1879, 1885, undated
  Rogers, P. V.: 1877, 1878, 1884
  Rogers, Sherman (?) S.: 1892
  Rollins, Alice H.: undated
  Rollins, D. M.: 1898 (see Reel 2323)
  Ruggles, H. M.: 1881, undated
  S
  St. Augustine Historical Society: 1930
  Saint-Gaudens, August: 1878, undated
  Sampson, Henry: 1875, 1876, undated
  Sargent, Amy (Mrs. John): undated
  Sargent, John: undated
  Sartorio, G. A.: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Schoff, ----: 1880
  Schuyler, Eugene: 1880 (see Reel 2323)
  Scott, Charles E.: 1910
  Scott, V. C.: 1909
  Scribner and Co.: 1881
  Scudder, Winthrop: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Sellstadt, Lars: 1884
  Sharp, William: undated
  Shaw, Louisa: 1872
  Sheldon, George William: 1889
  Sherman, Florence Bagley: 1895, undated
  Shillaber, Cynthia H.: 1877, 1878, 1879, undated
  Simmons, Franklin: 1876
  Simonds, George: 1869, 1871, 1877, 1884
  Simonds, Gertrude: 1893, undated
  Skillman, Jenny: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Skinner, Charles M.: 1880
  Smith, Anna Leigh: 1889, undated
  Smith, Robert M.: 1914
  South Carolina Inter-State and West Indian Exposition: 1901, 1902
  Special Committee on Casts, Metropolitan Museum of Art: 1895
  Speed, Hattina: 1938
  Stearns, J.: undated
  Stetson, Grace Elly Chaning: 1907, 1934
  Stewardson, T.: 1881
  Stillman, H. J.: 1878
  Stillman, W.: undated
  Stimson, D. M.: undated
  Stimson, Edith: undated
  Stoddard, Charles Warren: 1877 (see Reel 2323)
  Stoddard, R. H.: 1882
  Stokes, Whitley: 1905 (see Reel 2323)
  Stone, M. A.: 1880
  Story, Evelyn: undated
  Story, W. W.: 1877 (see Reel 2323)
  Srokosch, Clara Louise Kellog: 1913 (see Reel 2323)
  Strong, Alonzo P.: 1887
  T
  Tappan, Caroline: 1896, undated
  Tarkington, Louise (Mrs. Booth): 1905
  Thaxter, Celia: 1880 (see Reel 2323)
  Thaxter, L. L.: undated
  Thomas, Mary: undated
  Thompson, E.A.M.: undated
  Thompson, Eden Frances: 1887, 1889
  Thompson, Launt: 1878
  Thorndike, Mary and Henry A.: 1902, undated
  Ticknor and Fields: 1863
  Tildes, L----: 1878
  Tracy (Roudebush), Agnes: 1879, 1886-1888, 1891-1893, 1899, undated
  Tracy, Francis W.: 1879
  Turner, Russ: 1888, 1889
  Tuthill, William H.: 1914
  Tuttle, Mrs. B. B.: 1905
  U
  Underwood, M. Flora: 1898 (see Reel 2323)
  University Prints: 1938
  V
  Vanderbilt, Edith Stuyvesant: 1890 (see Reel 2323)
  Vaughan, Virginia: 1894, undated
  Vertunni, A.: 1878
  Volpi, E.: 1923
  W
  W. H. Smith: 1876, 1877
  Wagstaff, Ede: 1880
  Walters, W. J. (?): 1882
  Wakeman, Stephen H.: 1906 (see Reel 2323)
  Walthius, H. G.: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Ward, Edmund A.: 1871
  Warner, Charles Dudley: 1871
  Watrous, Harry W. (National Academy of Design): 1915
  Webb, Annie Bertram: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Welling, Genevieve: undated
  Wells, Clara L.: 1875, 1876
  Weston, Karl E.: 1938
  Wheatland, Maria: 1898, undated
  White, Bessie S. (Mrs. Stanford): 1937, undated
  White, Stanford: 1891 (see Reel 2323), undated
  Whiteford, Sidney J.: 1907
  Whitehouse, Remsen: undated (see Reel 2323)
  Whiting, Lilian: 1914
  Whittier, Charles A.: 1884, 1885, undated
  Willart, Laura: undated
  Williams, Henry D. (Williams and Everett): 1880, 1881
  Williams and Everett: 1891
  Wilmarth, Anna H.: undated
  Wilmarth, Mary H.: 1897
  Wilson, Anna: undated
  Wilson, M. B.: undated
  Winter, William: 1880 (see Reel 2323)
  Wood, Miles: 1880
  Woodhouse, Emma: 1878, 1879, undated
  Woodruff, Edith: undated (see Reel 2323)
  World's Fair, St. Louis: 1904
  Wright, Helen Keeps (Mrs. Orville B. Wright): 1938
  Wright, Mary Francis: 1890
  Y
  Yale University: 1930
  Yewell, George: 1870, 1871, 1872, 1872 (illustrated), 1881
  Yewell, Mollie: 1872, 1879
  Young, Mrs. Edward: 1938
  - Correspondence, 1804 (Reel 515, Frame 780-784)
  - Correspondence, 1826 (Reel 515, Frame 785-792)
  - Correspondence, 1835 (Reel 515, Frame 793-796)
  - Correspondence, 1842 (Reel 515, Frame 797-803)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1843 (Reel 515, Frame 804-837)
  - Correspondence, May-December 1843 (Reel 515, Frame 838-872)
  - Correspondence, 1844 (Reel 515, Frame 873-907)
  - Correspondence, 1845-1849 (Reel 515, Frame 908-942)
  - Correspondence, 1850 (Reel 515, Frame 944-976)
  - Correspondence, 1851 (Reel 515, Frame 977-993)
  - Correspondence, 1852-1859 (Reel 515, Frame 994-1065)
  - Correspondence, 1860 (Reel 515, Frame 1066-1086)
  - Correspondence, 1861 (Reel 515, Frame 1087-1105)
  - Correspondence, 1862 (Reel 515, Frame 1106-1141)
  - Correspondence, 1863-1864 (Reel 515, Frame 1142-1196)
  - Correspondence, 1865 (Reel 515, Frame 1197-1253)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1866 (Reel 515, Frame 1254-1287)
  - Correspondence, March-December 1866 (Reel 516, Frame 1-62)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1867 (Reel 516, Frame 63-130)
  - Correspondence, July-December 1867 (Reel 516, Frame 131-192)
  - Correspondence, 1868 (Reel 516, Frame 193-259)
  - Correspondence, 1869 (Reel 516, Frame 260-332)
  - Correspondence, January-July 1870 (Reel 516, Frame 334-393)
  - Correspondence, August-December 1870 (Reel 516, Frame 394-456)
  - Correspondence, 1870 (Reel 2323, Frame 127)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 457-509)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 510-582)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 583-629)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 630-689)
  - Correspondence, September 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 690-735)
  - Correspondence, October 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 736-774)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1871 (Reel 516, Frame 775-821)
  - Correspondence, 1871 (Reel 2323, Frame 128-129)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 822-868)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 869-934)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 935-1006)
  - Correspondence, July 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1007-1071)
  - Correspondence, August 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1072-1167)
  - Correspondence, September 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1168-1240)
  - Correspondence, October 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1241-1264)
  - Correspondence, November 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1265-1309)
  - Correspondence, December 1872 (Reel 516, Frame 1310-1357)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1873 (Reel 516, Frame 1358-1410)
  - Correspondence, May-September 1873 (Reel 516, Frame 1411-1445)
  - Correspondence, October 1873 (Reel 516, Frame 1446-1479)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1873 (Reel 516, Frame 1480-1522)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1874 (Reel 516, Frame 1523-1584)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1874 (Reel 516, Frame 1585-1617)
  - Correspondence, May 1874 (Reel 516, Frame 1618-1656)
  - Correspondence, June 1-6, 1874 (Reel 516, Frame 1657-1685)
  - Correspondence, June 7-30, 1874 (Reel 517, Frame 1-34)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1874 (Reel 517, Frame 35-73)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1874 (Reel 517, Frame 74-116)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1875 (Reel 517, Frame 117-160)
  - Correspondence, May-September 1875 (Reel 517, Frame 161-206)
  - Correspondence, October-November 1875 (Reel 517, Frame 207-266)
  - Correspondence, December 1875 (Reel 517, Frame 267-286)
  - Correspondence, 1875 (Reel 2323, Frame 130-136)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 287-341)
  - Correspondence, April-May 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 342-388)
  - Correspondence, June 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 389-453)
  - Correspondence, July 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 454-488)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 489-526)
  - Correspondence, October-November 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 527-573)
  - Correspondence, December 1876 (Reel 517, Frame 574-598)
  - Correspondence, 1876 (Reel 2323, Frame 137-138)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1877 (Reel 517, Frame 599-651)
  - Correspondence, March-August 1877 (Reel 517, Frame 652-699)
  - Correspondence, September-November 1877 (Reel 517, Frame 700-745)
  - Correspondence, December 1877 (Reel 517, Frame 746-772)
  - Correspondence, 1877 (Reel 2323, Frame 139-147)
  - Correspondence, January 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 773-836)
  - Correspondence, February-March 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 837-872)
  - Correspondence, April 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 873-917)
  - Correspondence, May 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 918-961)
  - Correspondence, June-July 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 962-1017)
  - Correspondence, August-October 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 1018-1065)
  - Correspondence, November 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 1066-1106)
  - Correspondence, 1-15 December 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 1107-1168)
  - Correspondence, 16-30 December 1878 (Reel 517, Frame 1169-1225)
  - Correspondence, January 1879 (Reel 517, Frame 1226-1267)
  - Correspondence, February-20 March 1879 (Reel 517, Frame 1268-1310)
  - Correspondence, 22 March-April 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 1-47)
  - Correspondence, May-July 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 48-102)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 103-158)
  - Correspondence, October 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 159-187)
  - Correspondence, November 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 188-257)
  - Correspondence, 1-15 December 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 258-292)
  - Correspondence, 16-30 December 1879 (Reel 518, Frame 293-330)
  - Correspondence, 1879 (Reel 2323, Frame 148-151)
  - Correspondence, 1-16 January 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 332-382)
  - Correspondence, 17-31 Janauary 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 383-444)
  - Correspondence, 1-14 February 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 445-499)
  - Correspondence, 15-28 February 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 500-540)
  - Correspondence, March 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 541-604)
  - Correspondence, 1-15 April 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 605-649)
  - Correspondence, 16-30 April 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 650-684)
  - Correspondence, 1-15 May 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 685-732)
  - Correspondence, 16-31 May 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 733-768)
  - Correspondence, June 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 769-817)
  - Correspondence, July 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 818-880)
  - Correspondence, August-October 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 881-937)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1880 (Reel 518, Frame 938-987)
  - Correspondence, 1880 (Reel 2323, Frame 152-175)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1881 (Reel 518, Frame 988-1017)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1881 (Reel 518, Frame 1018-1067)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1881 (Reel 518, Frame 1068-1108)
  - Correspondence, July-October 1881 (Reel 518, Frame 1109-1157)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1881 (Reel 518, Frame 1158-1197)
  - Correspondence, 1881 (Reel 2323, Frame 176-177)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1198-1249)
  - Correspondence, April-May 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1250-1293)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1294-1347)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1348-1403)
  - Correspondence, November 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1404-1442)
  - Correspondence, December 1882 (Reel 518, Frame 1443-1489)
  - Correspondence, 1882 (Reel 2323, Frame 178-180)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1883 (Reel 518, Frame 1490-1552)
  - Correspondence, March-December 1883 (Reel 518, Frame 1553-1610)
  - Correspondence, January-June 1884 (Reel 518, Frame 1611-1655)
  - Correspondence, July-October 1884 (Reel 518, Frame 1656-1683)
  - Correspondence, November 1884 (Reel 518, Frame 1684-1728)
  - Correspondence, 1-14 December 1884 (Reel 518, Frame 1729-1765)
  - Correspondence, 15-30 December 1884 (Reel 518, Frame 1766-1810)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1885 (Reel 518, Frame 1811-1847)
  - Correspondence, April-16 May 1885 (Reel 518, Frame 1848-1865)
  - Correspondence, 17 May-June 1885 (Reel 519, Frame 1-46)
  - Correspondence, July 1885 (Reel 519, Frame 47-71)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1885 (Reel 519, Frame 72-121)
  - Correspondence, October-November 1885 (Reel 519, Frame 122-171)
  - Correspondence, December 1885 (Reel 519, Frame 172-198)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1886 (Reel 519, Frame 199-246)
  - Correspondence, April-May 1886 (Reel 519, Frame 247-299)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1886 (Reel 519, Frame 300-364)
  - Correspondence, September-November 1886 (Reel 519, Frame 365-420)
  - Correspondence, 1886 (Reel 2323, Frame 183-184)
  - Correspondence, January 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 421-468)
  - Correspondence, February 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 469-512)
  - Correspondence, 1-15 March 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 513-568)
  - Correspondence, 16-31 March 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 569-636)
  - Correspondence, 1-11 April 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 637-677)
  - Correspondence, 12-30 April 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 678-726)
  - Correspondence, 1-18 May 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 727-769)
  - Correspondence, 19-31 May 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 770-812)
  - Correspondence, June 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 813-865)
  - Correspondence, July 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 866-918)
  - Correspondence, August 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 919-966)
  - Correspondence, September 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 967-1035)
  - Correspondence, October 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 1036-1077)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1887 (Reel 519, Frame 1078-1119)
  - Correspondence, 1887 (Reel 2323, Frame 181-182)
  - Correspondence, 1887 (Reel 2323, Frame 185-186)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1120-1153)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1154-1216)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1217-1258)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1259-1283)
  - Correspondence, October 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1284-1321)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1888 (Reel 519, Frame 1322-1387)
  - Correspondence, 1888 (Reel 2323, Frame 187-192)
  - Correspondence, January 1889 (Reel 519, Frame 1388-1429)
  - Correspondence, February 1889 (Reel 519, Frame 1430-1465)
  - Correspondence, March 1889 (Reel 519, Frame 1466-1485)
  - Correspondence, April 1889 (Reel 519, Frame 1486-1535)
  - Correspondence, May-10 June 1889 (Reel 519, Frame 1536-1582)
  - Correspondence, 11-30 June 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 1-33)
  - Correspondence, July 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 34-83)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 84-136)
  - Correspondence, October 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 137-178)
  - Correspondence, November 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 179-219)
  - Correspondence, 1-11 December 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 220-278)
  - Correspondence, 12-22 December 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 279-309)
  - Correspondence, 23-31 December 1889 (Reel 520, Frame 310-361)
  - Correspondence, 1889 (Reel 2323, Frame 193)
  - Correspondence, 1-21 January 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 363-414)
  - Correspondence, 22-31 January 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 415-447)
  - Correspondence, February 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 448-503)
  - Correspondence, March 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 504-575)
  - Correspondence, April 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 576-623)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 624-669)
  - Correspondence, July 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 670-706)
  - Correspondence, August 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 707-750)
  - Correspondence, September 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 751-796)
  - Correspondence, October 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 797-827)
  - Correspondence, November 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 828-880)
  - Correspondence, December 1890 (Reel 520, Frame 881-923)
  - Correspondence, 1890 (Reel 2323, Frame 194-213)
  - Correspondence, January 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 924-981)
  - Correspondence, February 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 982-1042)
  - Correspondence, March 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1043-1104)
  - Correspondence, April 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1105-1163)
  - Correspondence, May 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1164-1215)
  - Correspondence, June 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1216-1266)
  - Correspondence, July 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1267-1305)
  - Correspondence, 1-14 August 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1306-1350)
  - Correspondence, 15-31 August 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1351-1397)
  - Correspondence, 1-10 September 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1398-1443)
  - Correspondence, 11-30 September 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1444-1480)
  - Correspondence, October 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1481-1518)
  - Correspondence, November 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1519-1557)
  - Correspondence, December 1891 (Reel 520, Frame 1558-1594)
  - Correspondence, 1891 (Reel 2323, Frame 214-226)
  - Correspondence, 1-25 January 1892 (Reel 520, Frame 1595-1664)
  - Correspondence, 31 January-February 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 1-33)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 34-90)
  - Correspondence, May 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 91-134)
  - Correspondence, June-July 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 135-184)
  - Correspondence, August 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 185-246)
  - Correspondence, September 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 247-287)
  - Correspondence, October 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 288-333)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1892 (Reel 521, Frame 334-371)
  - Correspondence, 1892 (Reel 2323, Frame 227-257)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 372-445)
  - Correspondence, March-May 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 446-510)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 511-571)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 572-624)
  - Correspondence, November 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 625-663)
  - Correspondence, December 1893 (Reel 521, Frame 664-713)
  - Correspondence, 1893 (Reel 2323, Frame 258-266)
  - Correspondence, 1-20 January 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 714-750)
  - Correspondence, 21-31 January 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 751-809)
  - Correspondence, 1-10 February 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 810-859)
  - Correspondence, 11-18 February 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 860-909)
  - Correspondence, 19-28 February 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 910-965)
  - Correspondence, 1-20 March 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 966-1004)
  - Correspondence, 20-31 March 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1005-1067)
  - Correspondence, April 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1068-1136)
  - Correspondence, May 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1137-1195)
  - Correspondence, June 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1196-1262)
  - Correspondence, 1-10 July 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1263-1307)
  - Correspondence, 11-31 July 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1308-1357)
  - Correspondence, August-September 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1358-1419)
  - Correspondence, October 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1420-1475)
  - Correspondence, November 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1476-1525)
  - Correspondence, December 1894 (Reel 521, Frame 1526-1594)
  - Correspondence, 1894 (Reel 2323, Frame 267-277)
  - Correspondence, January-10 February 1895 (Reel 521, Frame 1595-1644)
  - Correspondence, 11 February-April 1895 (Reel 522, Frame 1-52)
  - Correspondence, May-August 1895 (Reel 522, Frame 53-102)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1895 (Reel 522, Frame 103-131)
  - Correspondence, 1895 (Reel 2323, Frame 278-287)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 132-178)
  - Correspondence, March 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 179-239)
  - Correspondence, April 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 240-275)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 276-339)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 340-406)
  - Correspondence, September-November 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 407-450)
  - Correspondence, December 1896 (Reel 522, Frame 451-496)
  - Correspondence, 1896 (Reel 2323, Frame 288-297)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1897 (Reel 522, Frame 497-552)
  - Correspondence, March-June 1897 (Reel 522, Frame 553-606)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1897 (Reel 522, Frame 607-646)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1897 (Reel 522, Frame 647-702)
  - Correspondence, 1897 (Reel 2323, Frame 298-311)
  - Correspondence, January-April 1898 (Reel 522, Frame 703-741)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1898 (Reel 522, Frame 742-797)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1898 (Reel 522, Frame 798-845)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1898 (Reel 522, Frame 846-873)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1898 (Reel 522, Frame 874-904)
  - Correspondence, 1898 (Reel 2323, Frame 312-340)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1899 (Reel 522, Frame 905-948)
  - Correspondence, April 1899 (Reel 522, Frame 949-1044)
  - Correspondence, May 1899 (Reel 522, Frame 1045-1116)
  - Correspondence, June-October 1899 (Reel 522, Frame 1117-1152)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1899 (Reel 522, Frame 1153-1213)
  - Correspondence, 1899 (Reel 2323, Frame 341-359)
  - Correspondence, January 1900 (Reel 522, Frame 1215-1306)